I love you, Penny!
(Sheldon:)How is it I can conceptualize
a methodology
(Sheldon:)of examining dark matter
in the universe
(Sheldon:)but can't figure out how
to fix a novelty squirt flower?
(Amy:)I think the real question is,
(Amy:)why do you waste your time
with cheap, childish pranks?
(Sheldon:)There's probably a deep reason,
(Sheldon:)which I'd be happy
to discuss with you
(Sheldon:)over some peanut brittle in a can.
Okay, Sheldon, I am out of options!
(Leonard:)Video store owner, Nursis Manookian,
has no next of kin!
(Sheldon:)Well, you seem hot
under the collar...
(Sheldon:)Or is that the sweater?
(Leonard:)Oh, oh, no, no.
It's because I spent all afternoon
(Leonard:)at the Armenian church
where his funeral mass was held.
(Leonard:)According to Father Solakian,
(Leonard:)no one attended.
(Leonard:)Luckily, my trip
wasn't a complete waste.
(Leonard:)I lit a candle
and prayed for your death.
(Leonard:)But I'm not Armenian,
so it probably won't work!
(Leonard:)This is over, right?
(Sheldon:)Oh, not necessarily.